breederretriever.com 2016-04-03

# Breeder Retriever - A Fun Website About Dogs and Puppies

Effective 05/04/2007

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

To quickly process your transactions.

**Collection of Personally Identifiable Information**

BreederRetriever.com does collect some personally identifiable information to permit advanced and interactive functionality. This information is collected via web forms filled out by our visitors and may include (but is not limited to) name, e-mail, username, business name, breeds (for breeders), address, phone number, fax, website address, BreederRetriever.com passwords, breeder related services offered, a business description, etc. 

To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature. 

**How do we protect visitor information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

**Do we use "cookies"?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We do link the information we store in cookies to some personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. Specifically, cookies our used for management of user account logins and sessions. The personally identifiable information that may be linked to a cookie includes (but is not limited to) name, e-mail, username, business name, breeds (for breeders), address, phone number, fax, website address, BreederRetriever.com passwords, breeder related services offered, a business description, etc.

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. We use a third-party tracking service called Google Analytics that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate such as usage and volume statistics (e.g. identification of our web traffic sources, our content usage and performance, etc.) to help us improve our site and understand where our web traffic is coming from. 

Some of our business partners (e.g. advertisers) may use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by BreederRetriever.com only and does not cover the user of cookies by any advertisers. 

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete, or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page (click log in on the navigation menu and clicking view / update / edit or by e-mailing our Customer Support at kkibak@breederretriever.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

**Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice and choice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include Your Best Deals. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Additionally, we reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

**Publicly Displayed Information**

If you use a bulletin board, blog, chat room, or breeder registration on this web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums/sections of our site, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums and aforementioned areas. 

**Communications from the Site**

**_Special Offers and Updates_**

We may occasionally send you information on special offers, promotions, site updates, newsletters, etc. Users can sign up for these e-mails by registering with BreederRetriever.com either as a breeder, a normal user, a forum member, or simply as a newsletter subscriber. 

Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. Please see "Choice and Opt-out."

**_Service Related Announcements_**

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an e-mail.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account by contacting us via e-mail. 

**_Customer Service_**

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by e-mail or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. 

**_Choice / Opt-out_**

We provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information. For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions in each newsletter or communication or by e-mailing us using our contact form or directly at kkibak@breederretriever.com. 

How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?

To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.

To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.

**Third party links**

In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and/or other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or be means of a notice on our home page. 

**Questions and feedback**

We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue. You can e-mail us at kkibak@breederretriever.com. Our physical mailing address is listed below. 

**Mailing Address**

1305 Gateview Avenue, Unit C

San Francisco, CA 94130

**Please Note:**

BreederRetriever.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build user's trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the web site BreederRetriever.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its informational practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Kris Kibak at kkibak@breederretriever.com. If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php 

TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

**Online Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
